1.0	spokesman	tell	afp	0	0
1.0	detonators	have	cache	O	O
1.0	regional government spokesman	confirm	nature of substance	0	0
1.0	cache	have	December discovery	O	O
1.0	Spain	in	basque region	LOCATION	0
1.0	explosive	of kilo be	200 pound	0	MONEY
1.0	Spain	have	region	O	LOCATION
1.0	explosives	have	kilos	O	O
1.0	Amorebieta	be in	north of basque region	LOCATION	0
1.0	ETA	be by	basque	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	region	have	north	O	O
1.0	substance	have	nature	O	O
1.0	police	be in	Spain 's basque region	0	LOCATION
1.0	government spokesman	confirm	nature of substance	0	0
1.0	explosives	have	cache	O	O
