1.0	Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki	have	government	O	PERSON
1.0	his	have	death warrant	O	O
0.44880808691637974	nothing	do with	any of procedure	0	0
1.0	him	have	control	O	O
1.0	it	be	sovereign nation	0	0
1.0	Saddam Hussein	have	US allies	O	O
1.0	Saddam	capture by	nine month later US commando	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	justice prison	have	ministry	O	O
1.0	Saddam	be	overthrow	PERSON	0
1.0	footage	later distribute on	internet	0	0
0.49043618890972485	scene	widely distribute across	Middle East	0	LOCATION
1.0	Saddam	have	control	O	PERSON
1.0	he death sentence	be	uphold	0	0
1.0	you	have	nothing do	0	0
1.0	their	have	decision	O	O
0.6495555743120573	iraqi government	custody of	he	0	0
0.633593924617174	coalition spokesman Major General William Caldwell	say to	he interpreter	0	0
1.0	he	tell reporter at	he weekly conference	0	SET
1.0	US force	have hand control before	hanging	LOCATION	0
0.49043618890972485	scene	distribute by	cellphone	0	0
1.0	Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki 's shiite-led government	have launch	investigation	PERSON	0
1.0	Iraq	have	decision	O	LOCATION
1.0	foes	have	reference	O	O
1.0	coalition spokesman Major General William Caldwell	say farewell to	he interpreter	0	0
1.0	US force	have hand control to	official	LOCATION	0
1.0	procedures	have	any	O	O
1.0	Saddam	be overthrow in	March 2003	PERSON	DATE
1.0	he	be courteous to	always have he police guard	0	0
1.0	he	be courteous to	have he US military police guard	0	LOCATION
1.0	Saddam	have	fate	O	PERSON
1.0	reporter	be in	Baghdad	0	LOCATION
0.15377660881103794	we	move in	ministry	0	0
1.0	US personnel	have leave	prison facility	LOCATION	0
1.0	iraqi military prison	be in	north of city	0	0
1.0	Saddam	of	death	PERSON	0
1.0	our	have	decision	O	O
1.0	that	have	charge	O	O
0.7142997911981888	he	have to	always have he military police guard	0	0
1.0	scene	be	film	0	0
1.0	Saddam Hussein	have	neck	O	PERSON
1.0	Saddam in a military base outside Baghdad	have	control	O	O
0.7142997911981888	he	have to	always have he US military police guard	0	LOCATION
0.7142997911981888	he	have to	have he military police guard	0	0
1.0	he	tell reporter at	he conference	0	0
0.565090557529179	we	physical control of	he	0	0
1.0	footage	distribute on	internet	0	0
1.0	Saddam	have	death	O	PERSON
1.0	his	have	hanging	O	O
0.15377660881103794	we	move in	ministry of justice prison	0	0
1.0	I	get in	touch	0	0
1.0	Saddam	be	overthrow in March 2003 by us-led invasion	PERSON	DATE
1.0	US force	have hand	control of Saddam	LOCATION	PERSON
1.0	he	be courteous to	always have he military police guard	0	0
1.0	he	tell	reporter	0	0
1.0	footage	be	film on phone by iraqi official	0	0
0.49043618890972485	scene	widely distribute by	cellphone	0	0
1.0	leader	have	foes	O	O
1.0	his	have	conference	O	O
1.0	Saddam	be overthrow by	invasion	PERSON	0
1.0	footage	be	film on phone by official	0	0
1.0	his	have	death sentence	O	O
1.0	US army colonel	sign saddam over	over iraqi prison warden	LOCATION	0
0.7142997911981888	he	have to	have he police guard	0	0
1.0	we	have handle	physical control	0	0
1.0	he	be courteous to	have he military police guard	0	0
1.0	dictator Saddam Hussein	have	execution	O	PERSON
1.0	death	have	Footage	O	O
0.6495555743120573	iraqi government	legal custody of	he	0	0
1.0	Saddam Hussein	be of	iraqi	PERSON	0
1.0	US force	have hand	physical control	LOCATION	0
1.0	he death sentence	be	on December 26 uphold by appeal chamber	0	DATE
1.0	decision	be	make	0	0
1.0	Saddam	be	once take into execution chamber by he iraqi guard	PERSON	DATE
1.0	footage	be film by	iraqi official	0	0
1.0	Saddam	capture by	US commando	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	his	have	Sunni supporters	O	O
1.0	US force	have hand control to	iraqi official	LOCATION	0
1.0	his	have	police guards	O	O
1.0	Sadr	have	Mahdi Army militia	O	PERSON
1.0	Saddam	capture by	later US commando	PERSON	LOCATION
0.9192435451032213	US force	control of	Saddam Hussein	LOCATION	PERSON
1.0	their	have	responsibility	O	O
1.0	crimes	have	convicted	O	O
0.6495555743120573	government	legal custody of	he	0	0
1.0	Saddam Hussein	have	control	O	PERSON
1.0	control mechanisms	have	any	O	O
1.0	their	have	credibility	O	O
1.0	we	have handle	control	0	0
1.0	he	be courteous to	have he police guard	0	0
1.0	violence	have	much	O	O
1.0	as-buratha prison facility	ministry of	justice prison	0	0
1.0	Saddam	be	once take into execution chamber by iraqi guard	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Saddam	be overthrow by	us-led invasion	PERSON	0
1.0	Sadr	have	Mahdi Army militia for much of sectarian violence plague	PERSON	ORGANIZATION
1.0	I	get with	group	0	0
1.0	I	have	have able	0	0
1.0	US force	have hand control before	shortly hanging	LOCATION	0
1.0	he	be courteous to	always have he US military police guard	0	LOCATION
1.0	he death sentence	be uphold by	appeal chamber	0	0
1.0	Americans	have	group	O	MISC
1.0	execution	take	place	0	0
1.0	city	have	north	O	O
1.0	Saddam	be	overthrow in March 2003 by invasion	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Nuri al-Maliki	have	shiite-led government	PERSON	0
1.0	him	have	custody	O	O
1.0	he death sentence	be uphold on	December 26	0	DATE
1.0	US army colonel	sign	Saddam	LOCATION	PERSON
1.0	you	have	nothing do with any	0	0
1.0	footage	be	film on mobile phone by official	0	0
1.0	his	have	doctor	O	O
1.0	his	have	guards	O	O
0.15377660881103794	we	move in	as-buratha prison facility	0	0
1.0	we	move	he	0	0
1.0	villagers	have	murder	O	O
1.0	His	have	characterisation	O	O
1.0	footage	be film on	mobile phone	0	0
1.0	Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki 's government	have launch	investigation	PERSON	0
1.0	it	be	nation	0	0
1.0	scene	be	how film	0	0
0.7142997911981888	he	have to	always have he police guard	0	0
1.0	the Iraqi prison facility	take	place	0	0
1.0	Saddam	over	fate	PERSON	0
1.0	scene	have stir	anger	0	0
0.44880808691637974	nothing	do with	any	0	0
1.0	Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki 's	say	explain	0	0
1.0	coalition spokesman Major General William Caldwell	say	farewell	0	0
1.0	footage	be film by	official	0	0
1.0	coalition spokesman Major General William Caldwell	say at_time	Wednesday	PERSON	DATE
1.0	footage	be film on	phone	0	0
1.0	his	have	interpreter	O	O
1.0	decision	have	government	O	O
1.0	footage	be	film	0	0
0.49043618890972485	scene	distribute across	Middle East	0	LOCATION
1.0	you	have	nothing do with any of procedure	0	0
1.0	present	have	One	NUMBER	DATE
1.0	you	be ask	I	0	0
1.0	footage	be	film on mobile phone by iraqi official	0	0
0.9192435451032213	US force	physical control of	Saddam Hussein	LOCATION	PERSON
1.0	Saddam	have	moments	O	PERSON
0.6495555743120573	government	custody of	he	0	0
1.0	it	be	sovereign	0	0
0.565090557529179	we	control of	he	0	0
1.0	you	have	nothing	0	0
1.0	US personnel	have leave	iraqi prison facility	LOCATION	0
1.0	US force	have hand	physical control of Saddam	LOCATION	PERSON
1.0	US army colonel	sign saddam over	over prison warden	LOCATION	0
1.0	their	have	custody	O	O
1.0	US force	have hand	control	LOCATION	0
1.0	Saddam	be in	military base outside Baghdad	PERSON	LOCATION
0.7142997911981888	he	have to	have he US military police guard	0	LOCATION
1.0	him	have	movement	O	O
