1.0	Verizon Communications	be with	28.5 percent stake	ORGANIZATION	PERCENT
1.0	share	tumble in	New York	DURATION	LOCATION
1.0	its	have	autonomy	O	O
1.0	stock price	be in	Venezuela	0	DURATION
1.0	US	have	Verizon Communications	ORGANIZATION	LOCATION
1.0	share	tumble by	quarter on opening	DURATION	DURATION
1.0	30.26 percent	lose	Electricidad de Caracas	PERCENT	ORGANIZATION
1.0	percent	lose	Electricidad de Caracas	PERCENT	ORGANIZATION
1.0	whose	have	main	O	O
1.0	President Hugo Chavez	nationalize	power sector	PERSON	0
1.0	stock price	plunge on	Tuesday	0	DURATION
1.0	share	tumble by	quarter	DURATION	DURATION
1.0	crude	have	refineries	O	O
1.0	laws	have	mother	O	O
1.0	Monday	from	close	DATE	0
1.0	country	have	bank	O	O
1.0	share	be in	CANTV	DURATION	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Monday	have	close	O	DATE
1.0	autonomy	have	bank	O	O
1.0	share	tumble off by	quarter on opening	DURATION	DURATION
1.0	trading	have	close	O	O
1.0	share	tumble off by	quarter	DURATION	DURATION
1.0	share price	decline	18.66 percent	0	PERCENT
1.0	stock price	plunge at_time	day	0	DURATION
1.0	refineries	have	control	O	O
1.0	Monday	below	close	DATE	0
1.0	share	tumble off in	New York	DURATION	LOCATION
