1.0	Cancer Research UK	's director be	Lesley Walker	ORGANIZATION	PERSON
1.0	smoking	take	plenty of exercise	0	0
1.0	exercise	have	plenty	O	O
1.0	cancer information	of director be	Lesley Walker	0	PERSON
1.0	cases	have	half	O	O
1.0	Cancer Research UK	have	director of cancer information	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	their risk of getting cancer	be out of	they hand	0	0
1.0	smoker	be more likely than	non-smoker	0	0
1.0	smoking	keep	healthy weight	0	0
1.0	smoking	take	plenty exercise	0	0
1.0	percent	have	total	O	PERCENT
1.0	British people	have	lifestyle choices	O	O
1.0	British people	have	percent	PERCENT	O
1.0	British people	have	doctor	O	O
1.0	population	have	percentage	O	O
1.0	we	can all reduce	we risk	0	0
1.0	smoking	keep	weight	0	0
1.0	we	can reduce	we risk	0	0
1.0	healthy weight	eat	balanced diet	0	0
1.0	draw	have	luck	O	O
1.0	figure	rise among	those from area	0	0
1.0	smoker	be	likely	0	0
1.0	figure	rise among	those from deprive area	0	0
1.0	cancer	choice	British people	DURATION	0
1.0	British people	notice	anything abnormal	0	0
1.0	sun	avoid also	sunburn	0	0
1.0	vegetables	have	plenty	O	O
1.0	Cancer Research UK 's director	describe	result as worry	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	weight	eat	balanced diet	0	0
1.0	healthy weight	eat	diet	0	0
1.0	people	have	quarter	DURATION	O
1.0	sun	avoid	sunburn	0	0
1.0	cancer	have	cases	O	O
1.0	smokers	have	risk	O	O
1.0	figure	fall in	privileged area	0	0
1.0	more than 4,000 adults across the country	have	risk	O	O
1.0	we	can reduce	we risk of cancer	0	0
1.0	we	can all reduce	we risk of cancer	0	0
0.6077979669577646	take	plenty of	exercise	0	0
0.6077979669577646	take	plenty	exercise	0	0
1.0	weight	eat	diet	0	0
1.0	destiny	have	matter	O	O
1.0	Cancer Research UK	have	director	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	smoker	be likely than	non-smoker	0	0
1.0	cancer information	have	director	O	O
1.0	fruit	have	plenty	O	O
1.0	figure	rise to	43 percent	0	PERCENT
1.0	figure	rise among	those	0	0
1.0	cancer	have	risk	O	O
1.0	smoker	be	more likely	0	0
1.0	figure	rise among	those from most deprive area	0	0
1.0	British people	notice	abnormal	0	0
1.0	more than 4,000 adults across the country	have	hands	O	O
1.0	we	stop	smoking	0	0
1.0	adults	have	poll	O	O
1.0	figure	fall in	most privileged area	0	0
