1.0	the	come from	oven	0	0
1.0	Singh	have	Orlando apartment	O	PERSON
1.0	her baby	have	baby	O	O
1.0	his	have	brother	O	O
1.0	Singh	at	Orlando apartment	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	her baby	have	apartment	O	O
1.0	brother	have	belongings	O	O
1.0	oven	have	area	O	O
1.0	police	say at_time	Wednesday	0	DATE
1.0	uncle	remove	child	0	0
1.0	baby	on	body	0	0
1.0	Sharlyn Singh	be	29	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	his	have	question	O	O
1.0	bail	have	remained	O	O
1.0	Singh	leave	apartment	PERSON	0
1.0	Guyana	have	citizen	O	LOCATION
1.0	baby	have	body	O	O
1.0	Sharlyn Singh	citizen of	Guyana	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	Singh	ignore	he question	PERSON	0
1.0	the cry	come from	oven	0	0
1.0	baby	have	uncle	O	O
