1.0	move	be	latest chapter	0	0
1.0	move	be latest chapter in	long run dispute	0	0
1.0	move	be latest chapter in	long dispute	0	0
1.0	UCI Pro Tour	have	development	O	O
1.0	Cycling 's three biggest races are to be taken to the European Commission by the International Cycling Union -LRB- UCI -RRB-	have	Tour series	O	O
1.0	UCI 's main gripe	be with	France	ORGANIZATION	LOCATION
1.0	the UCI	have	main gripe with Tour de France	ORGANIZATION	LOCATION
1.0	Cycling	have	Cycling 's three biggest races are to be taken to the European Commission by the International Cycling Union -LRB- UCI -RRB-	O	O
1.0	UCI	decide against	orgainser of Tours	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	competition	have	laws	O	O
1.0	Tours	have	orgainsers	O	O
1.0	Cycling	have	three biggest race	ORGANIZATION	NUMBER
1.0	Tours	have	organisers	O	O
1.0	sport	between	ruling body	0	0
1.0	UCI	explain in	statement	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	UCI 's main gripe	be restriction	they place	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	UCI	decide against	orgainser	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	UCI 's gripe	be restriction	they place on choice	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	move	be chapter in	run dispute	0	0
1.0	Tours	have	Organisers	O	MISC
1.0	move	be	chapter	0	0
1.0	organiser	sabotage	development	0	0
1.0	organiser	sabotage	development of UCI pro Tour	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	the UCI	have	gripe	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Hein Verbruggen	be by	UCI	PERSON	ORGANIZATION
1.0	teams	have	choice	O	O
1.0	latest chapter	be in	long run dispute between sport 's ruling body	0	0
1.0	UCI	decide against	orgainser of main Tours	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	move	be latest chapter in	dispute	0	0
1.0	they	place on	choice	0	0
1.0	move	be chapter in	dispute	0	0
1.0	Italy	have	Tour	O	LOCATION
1.0	move	be latest chapter in	run dispute	0	0
1.0	move	be chapter in	long dispute	0	0
1.0	sport	have	ruling body	O	O
1.0	UCI	explain in	statement Tuesday	ORGANIZATION	DATE
1.0	Spain	have	Tour	O	LOCATION
1.0	UCI 's gripe	be restriction	they place	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	their	have	position	O	O
1.0	their	have	events	O	O
1.0	Hein Verbruggen	be president of	UCI	PERSON	ORGANIZATION
1.0	three jewel	be in	cycling calendar	NUMBER	0
1.0	move	be chapter in	long run dispute	0	0
1.0	UCI	decide at_time	today	ORGANIZATION	DATE
1.0	UCI 's main gripe	be restriction	they place on choice	ORGANIZATION	0
