1.0	Bulgarians	have	percent	PERCENT	MISC
1.0	past	have	thing	O	DATE
1.0	partners	have	solidarity	O	O
1.0	Foreign Minister Ivaylo Kalfin	tell	national radio	PERSON	0
1.0	poorest country	be in	enlarged bloc	0	0
1.0	Romania	be	Bulgaria	LOCATION	LOCATION
0.4841922320533058	Eurobarometer poll	conduct on	eve	MISC	0
1.0	Sofia	reach	solution in case of we nurse	LOCATION	0
1.0	requirements	have	system	O	O
1.0	facilities	have	opening	O	O
1.0	bulgarian nurse	sentence	palestinian doctor	0	0
1.0	future	have	part	O	DATE
1.0	plenty	have	horn	O	O
1.0	Sofia	reach	just solution in case of we nurse	LOCATION	0
1.0	population	have	percent	PERCENT	O
1.0	Sofia	reach	solution in case	LOCATION	0
1.0	death	be in	December 31	0	DATE
1.0	President Georgy Parvanov	have	people	O	O
1.0	Bulgaria	at	single nuclear power plant at Kozloduy	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	nurses	have	release	O	O
1.0	Bulgaria	of	accession	LOCATION	0
1.0	President Georgy Parvanov	urge	he people	PERSON	0
1.0	solution	be in	case of we nurse	0	0
1.0	Bulgaria	have	accession	O	LOCATION
1.0	Sofia	reach	just solution	LOCATION	0
0.4841922320533058	Eurobarometer poll	conduct on	eve Bulgaria accession	MISC	LOCATION
1.0	reactor	part of	common future	0	DATE
1.0	Sofia	count on	solidarity of its partner	LOCATION	0
1.0	five bulgarian nurse	sentence	palestinian doctor	0	0
1.0	reactor	part of	common european future	0	DATE
1.0	Foreign Minister Ivaylo Kalfin	tell	radio	PERSON	0
1.0	Sofia	reach solution in	Libya	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	Sofia	reach	solution	LOCATION	0
1.0	Bulgaria	have	power plant	O	LOCATION
1.0	country	have	entry	O	O
1.0	visible result	be in	fight against crime	0	0
1.0	President Georgy Parvanov	also urge	he people	PERSON	0
1.0	Sofia	count on	solidarity of its european partner	LOCATION	0
1.0	union	have	most enthusiastic newcomer	0	0
1.0	union	have	newcomers	O	O
1.0	he	accuse	country 's last two government	0	NUMBER
1.0	reactor	part of	european future	0	DATE
1.0	Sofia	reach	just solution in case	LOCATION	0
1.0	nurses	have	case	O	O
1.0	country	have	last two government have cede	0	NUMBER
1.0	negotiation	be with	European Union	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	population	be in	eu-25	0	0
1.0	Sofia	count on	solidarity	LOCATION	0
1.0	their	have	country	O	O
1.0	interest	have	part	O	O
1.0	he	accuse	country 's two government	0	NUMBER
1.0	reactor	part of	future	0	DATE
1.0	two	have	closure	O	NUMBER
1.0	Sofia	have	partners	O	O
1.0	rules	have	system	O	O
1.0	parliament	have	session	O	O
1.0	our	have	nurses	O	O
1.0	accession	have	eve	O	O
1.0	country	have	governments	O	O
