1.0	US Senator John McCain on Thursday	have	support	O	O
1.0	war	have	Navy pilot	O	O
1.0	it	be go	difficult	0	0
1.0	John McCain	be	the United States	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	troop surge	have find support in	Congress	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	John McCain	be senator of	the United States	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	Bush	announce	shakeup	PERSON	0
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	early frontrunner for	presidential nomination	PERSON	0
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	early frontrunner for	republican nomination	PERSON	0
1.0	former Navy pilot	tell	MSNBC	ORGANIZATION	ORGANIZATION
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	early frontrunner for	2008 republican nomination	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Senate Armed Services Committee	be in	democrat-led	ORGANIZATION	0
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	frontrunner for	republican presidential nomination	PERSON	0
1.0	failure	have	consequences	O	O
1.0	troops	have	thousands	O	O
1.0	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	tell	MSNBC	PERSON	ORGANIZATION
1.0	troop surge	have find	little support	0	0
1.0	Republican	be in	Senate Armed Services Committee	MISC	ORGANIZATION
1.0	thousands	have	deployment	O	O
1.0	John McCain	be on	Thursday	PERSON	DATE
1.0	consequence	be	chaos	0	0
1.0	it	be go	very very difficult	0	0
1.0	US strategy	have	reassessment	O	O
1.0	their	have	November elections triumph	O	O
1.0	harm	into	way	0	0
1.0	Senate	have	control	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	troop surge	have find	support	0	0
1.0	world	have	parts	O	O
1.0	US Iraq policy	have	shakeup	O	O
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	early frontrunner for	republican presidential nomination	PERSON	0
1.0	George W. Bush	in	upcome reassessment of US strategy	PERSON	LOCATION
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	early frontrunner for	nomination	PERSON	0
1.0	America	have	want	O	LOCATION
1.0	His	have	remarks	O	O
1.0	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	have	hand	O	O
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	frontrunner for	presidential nomination	PERSON	0
1.0	Representatives	have	control	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	US troops	have	thousands	O	O
1.0	harm	have	way	O	O
1.0	policy	have	favor	O	O
1.0	US Senator John McCain	reaffirm	he support	LOCATION	0
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	frontrunner for	nomination	PERSON	0
1.0	President George W. Bush	have	reassessment	O	PERSON
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	frontrunner for	2008 republican presidential nomination	PERSON	DATE
1.0	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	frontrunner for	2008 republican presidential nomination	PERSON	DATE
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	frontrunner for	2008 republican nomination	PERSON	DATE
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	frontrunner for	republican nomination	PERSON	0
1.0	failure	have	sequences	O	O
1.0	troop surge	have find support with	McCain one	0	NUMBER
0.8625763634887544	McCain , an early frontrunner for the 2008 Republican presidential nomination	early frontrunner for	2008 republican presidential nomination	PERSON	DATE
1.0	House	have	control	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	it	be go	very difficult	0	0
