1.0	ex-wife	be film	smooch among wave	0	0
1.0	brazilian official	however tell	O Estado	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Rubens Decoussau	say	couple 's lawyer	PERSON	0
1.0	couple	have	lawyer	0	0
1.0	ex-wife	be film	smooch	0	0
1.0	official	however tell	O Estado	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	ex-wife	be film by	paparazzi	0	0
1.0	ex-wife	be	film	0	0
1.0	wave	be with	Renato Malzoni	0	PERSON
1.0	official	tell	O Estado	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	brazilian official	tell	O Estado	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	ex-wife	be film by	paparazzi at beach	0	0
1.0	brazilian official	however tell	O Estado de Sao Paulo newspaper	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	official	tell	O Estado de Sao Paulo newspaper	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Ronaldo	be of	brazilian	PERSON	0
1.0	ex-wife	be film by	paparazzi at beach in Cadiz	0	LOCATION
1.0	brazilian official	tell	O Estado de Sao Paulo newspaper	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	its	have	customers	O	O
1.0	ex-wife	smooch among	wave	0	0
1.0	couple	have	lawyer	O	O
1.0	soccer star Ronaldo	have	ex-wife	O	PERSON
1.0	beach	be in	Spain	0	LOCATION
1.0	official	however tell	O Estado de Sao Paulo newspaper	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	local newspaper	report at_time	Thursday	0	DATE
1.0	newspaper	report at_time	Thursday	0	DATE
1.0	supermodel Adriana Cicarelli	have	video	O	PERSON
1.0	beach	be in	Cadiz	0	LOCATION
