1.0	statute book	have	overhaul	O	O
1.0	Ireland	repeal	3,200 law date back	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	he descendant	be	monarch	0	0
1.0	country	have	chief law officer	O	O
1.0	country	have	chief law officer	0	0
1.0	Ireland	win	independence	LOCATION	0
1.0	he descendant	be monarch of	Ireland	0	LOCATION
1.0	laws	have	list	O	O
1.0	Vikings	have	descendants	O	PERSON
1.0	statutes	have	review	O	O
1.0	population	have	majority	O	O
1.0	Ahern	tell	journalist	PERSON	0
1.0	England	have	Norman invasion	O	LOCATION
1.0	Ahern	remove	as many law from statute book	PERSON	0
1.0	Ahern	tell journalist in	Dublin	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	Britain	have	authority	O	LOCATION
1.0	Bertie Ahern	be	irish	PERSON	0
1.0	laws	have	Many	O	O
1.0	Ahern	remove	many law from statute book	PERSON	0
1.0	Ahern	remove	almost as many law from statute book	PERSON	0
1.0	its	have	statute book	O	O
1.0	Ireland Act	have	Government	O	O
1.0	Ireland	have	monarchs	O	LOCATION
1.0	Ireland	repeal	3,200 law date	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	effect	be in	Ireland	0	LOCATION
1.0	it	be	design	0	0
1.0	Ireland	repeal	3,200 law	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	Ireland	win independence from	Britain	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	it	suppress	paganism	0	0
1.0	Ahern	remove	almost many law from statute book	PERSON	0
1.0	his	have	descendants	O	O
1.0	State	in	history	0	0
1.0	Ahern	remove	law from statute book	PERSON	0
1.0	Ireland	have	Norman conquest	O	LOCATION
1.0	State	have	history	O	O
1.0	England	have	King	O	LOCATION
1.0	measure	be in	State 's history	0	0
