1.0	Kenya	be expect	appeal for more humanitarian funding for Somalia	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	dictator Mohamed Siad Barre	have	ouster	O	PERSON
1.0	fighters	have	some	O	O
1.0	its	have	border	O	O
1.0	it	host	panel meeting	0	0
1.0	Somalia 's	have lack	effective government	LOCATION	0
1.0	Somalia 's	have	government	O	LOCATION
1.0	whom	have	some	O	O
1.0	their	have	families	O	O
1.0	Kenya	be expect	appeal for humanitarian funding for Somalia	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	combatants	have	Some	O	O
1.0	some	be	interrogate	0	0
1.0	Kenya	appeal for	humanitarian funding for Somalia	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	some	be	combatant	0	0
0.536066213907059	Nairobi	deport	at least 700 Somalis	LOCATION	MISC
1.0	some	hold	foreign passport	0	0
1.0	Somalia 's	have lack government since	1991 ouster	LOCATION	DATE
1.0	passports	have	holders	O	O
1.0	asylum seekers	have	some	O	O
1.0	authority	be in	Kenya	0	LOCATION
1.0	Some of these fighters	have	families	O	O
1.0	UNHCR	refuse entry to	thousand	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	it	be	apparent	0	0
1.0	Somalia 's	have lack	government	LOCATION	0
1.0	Somalia 's	have lack government since	1991 ouster of dictator Mohamed Siad Barre	LOCATION	PERSON
1.0	Foreign Minister Raphael Tuju	say	day	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	some	hold	passport	0	0
0.9666146225966369	Somalis	700 at	least	MISC	DURATION
1.0	Kenya	say at_time	Thursday	LOCATION	DATE
1.0	Foreign Minister Raphael Tuju	tell	press conference	PERSON	0
1.0	Kenya	be	expect	LOCATION	0
1.0	violence	have	state	O	O
1.0	Somalia	have	islamist movement	LOCATION	0
1.0	some	be combatant on	run	0	0
1.0	Kenya	appeal for	more humanitarian funding for Somalia	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	Somalia	have	movement	O	LOCATION
1.0	it	host	international panel meeting	0	0
1.0	civilians	have	thousands	O	O
1.0	it	explore	possibility	0	0
1.0	it	host panel meeting on	Friday	0	DATE
1.0	Africa nation	have	Horn	LOCATION	O
1.0	anarchy	have	state	O	O
1.0	armed conflict	be in	Mogadishu	0	LOCATION
1.0	Foreign Minister Raphael Tuju	tell press conference in	Nairobi	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	UNHCR	refuse	entry	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	fighters	have	Some	O	O
1.0	Foreign Minister Raphael Tuju	say	day UN refugee agency say	PERSON	DURATION
