1.0	I	even be innocent	proved	0	0
1.0	adherence	have	lack	O	O
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in era	PERSON	0
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in era	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	I	be	even innocent	0	0
1.0	I	be	innocent	0	0
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in era strip of Tour de France 's jersey	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	accomplishments	have	athlete	O	O
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in era strip	PERSON	0
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in modern era strip	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in era strip of Tour de France 's jersey	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in modern era	PERSON	0
1.0	their	have	lack	O	O
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in modern era strip of Tour de France 's yellow jersey	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in era strip of Tour de France 's yellow jersey	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider	PERSON	0
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in modern era strip of Tour de France 's jersey	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	would first rider	be in	modern era strip of Tour de France 's yellow jersey	ORDINAL	LOCATION
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in era strip	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Landis	have	spokesman	PERSON	0
1.0	connection	be with	he defence	0	MISC
1.0	Landis	have	spokesman	O	PERSON
1.0	his	have	teammate Oscar Pereiro	PERSON	O
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in modern era strip of Tour de France 's jersey	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in modern era strip of Tour de France 's yellow jersey	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	I	be innocent	proved	0	0
1.0	doping charges	have	name	O	O
1.0	American cyclist Floyd Landis	have	name	O	O
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would first rider in modern era	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Tour de France jersey	have	stripped	O	O
1.0	american cyclist Floyd Landis	raise	two million dollar	PERSON	MONEY
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in era strip of Tour de France 's yellow jersey	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	have	defence	O	O
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	find	guilty	PERSON	0
1.0	Floyd Landis	be	american	PERSON	0
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	would	would rider in modern era strip	PERSON	0
1.0	cyclist Floyd Landis	raise	two million dollar	PERSON	MONEY
1.0	American cyclist Floyd Landis	of	accomplishment	PERSON	0
1.0	Spain	have	teammate Oscar Pereiro	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	my reputation	be	ruin	0	0
1.0	Tour de France	have	jersey	O	LOCATION
1.0	Michael Henson	be spokesman of	Landis	PERSON	PERSON
1.0	France	of	yellow jersey	LOCATION	0
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	have	samples	O	O
1.0	athlete	have	those	O	O
1.0	American cyclist Floyd Landis	have	accomplishments	O	PERSON
1.0	US taxpayer dollars	have	dollar grants	O	O
1.0	my	have	reputation	O	O
1.0	jersey	have	stripped	O	O
1.0	Landis , who is expected to be stripped of the Tour de France yellow jersey for testing positive after the 2006 race	have	result	O	O
