1.0	Fisheries	have	Directorate	ORGANIZATION	ORGANIZATION
0.9718382584724056	farm	located in	fjord along Norway 's coast	0	LOCATION
1.0	it	be	dramatic	0	0
0.9718382584724056	farm	located in	fjord	0	0
1.0	fish	be	carrier	0	0
1.0	farm located	infect	young salmon	0	0
1.0	Authorities	have	controls	O	O
1.0	branch	have	Maren Esmark	PERSON	O
1.0	fish farms	have	list	O	O
1.0	farm located	infect	young wild salmon	0	0
1.0	farm located	infect	salmon	0	0
1.0	directorate	have	head	O	O
1.0	farm located	infect	wild salmon	0	0
0.9718382584724056	farm	located in	fjord along Norway 's west coast	0	LOCATION
1.0	Norway	have	coast	O	LOCATION
1.0	parasites	have	carriers	O	O
1.0	carriers of parasites such as sea lice , which infect wild salmon and other maritime life	have	systems	O	O
1.0	commission	have	July creation	O	O
1.0	head	tell	afp	0	0
1.0	fish	be carrier of	parasite	0	0
1.0	farm	infect	young wild salmon	0	0
1.0	farm	infect	salmon	0	0
1.0	39	have	total	O	NUMBER
1.0	farm	infect	young salmon	0	0
1.0	farm	infect salmon before	carriers of parasites such as sea lice , which infect wild salmon and other maritime life	0	0
1.0	security	be	criminal	0	0
1.0	Norway	along	west coast	LOCATION	0
1.0	farm	infect	wild salmon	0	0
1.0	salmon	have	cleansing	O	O
1.0	farm located	infect salmon before	carriers of parasites such as sea lice , which infect wild salmon and other maritime life	0	0
1.0	group WWF	have	branch	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Norwegian fish farms	have	39	NUMBER	O
