1.0	most people	even think of	cat	0	0
1.0	his	have	girlfriend	O	O
1.0	his	have	friend	O	O
1.0	game	have	hold	O	O
1.0	he daughter	tend	fire	0	0
1.0	cat	be eat with	degree spice to client 's taste	0	0
1.0	dish	have enter	local literature	0	0
1.0	chef	have	skill	O	O
1.0	flies	have	swarms	O	O
1.0	those disappointed	have	opinion	O	O
1.0	cat	be eat with	degree spice	0	0
1.0	cat	be eat with	degree spice to client 's taste accompany	0	0
1.0	cat	be	eat in soup with degree	0	0
1.0	his	have	partner	O	O
1.0	he	gradually attract	clientele	0	0
1.0	it	be hard in	Abidjan	0	LOCATION
1.0	himself	like cook be	sign	0	0
1.0	most people	even still think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	his	have	house	O	O
1.0	dish	have even enter	local literature	0	0
1.0	it	get	hold	0	0
1.0	cook	warn	he eager onlooker	0	0
1.0	cat	be	eat in soup with degree spice to client 's taste	0	0
1.0	people	even still think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	most people	still think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	dish	already be book	brushing	0	0
1.0	the meat	be	taboo	0	0
1.0	owl	have	that	O	O
1.0	Dabou Tcheke	age around	50	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	his	have	skills	O	O
1.0	it	here be hard in	Abidjan	0	LOCATION
1.0	people	eat	it	0	0
1.0	cat	have	fan	O	O
1.0	taboo	cook	the meat	0	0
1.0	dish	have even enter	literature	0	0
1.0	people	even still think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	most people	think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	people	even think of	cat	0	0
1.0	it	be	here hard	0	0
1.0	more people	eat	it	0	0
1.0	he	attract	clientele	0	0
1.0	he	be carpenter by	training	0	0
1.0	people	still think of	cat	0	0
1.0	cook	warn	he onlooker	0	0
1.0	most people	even think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	he	say with	touch	0	0
1.0	most people	even still think of	cat	0	0
1.0	he	deny	steal	0	0
1.0	Ivory Coast	have	state	O	LOCATION
1.0	he eager onlooker	cook in	spicy soup	0	0
1.0	skills	have	criticism	O	O
1.0	month	be	worth	DURATION	0
1.0	it	be	hard	0	0
1.0	cat	have	think	O	O
1.0	he	be	carpenter	0	0
1.0	cat	be eat with	degree	0	0
1.0	which	have	resembles	O	O
1.0	people	think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	his	have	onlookers	O	O
1.0	it	get	hold of game	0	0
1.0	his	have	suppliers	O	O
1.0	that	have	reminds	O	O
1.0	he youngest daughter	tend	fire	0	0
1.0	his	have	clients	O	O
1.0	Dabou Tcheke	ago could get	seven cat	0	DATE
0.6924625296193697	the meat	cook albeit	the meat	0	0
1.0	cat	have	taste	O	O
1.0	Nicolas Guede	wield	he cleaver	PERSON	0
1.0	most people	think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	My	have	clients	O	O
1.0	his	have	daughter	O	O
1.0	girlfriend	have	cat	O	O
1.0	he onlooker	cook in	spicy soup	0	0
1.0	house	have	cooks	O	O
1.0	country	have	west	O	O
1.0	Dabou Tcheke	could get	seven cat	0	DATE
1.0	Leon Sery	be among	those disappointed	PERSON	0
1.0	people	think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	most people	still think of	cat	0	0
1.0	Abidjan	have	known	O	LOCATION
1.0	cooks	have	heard	O	O
1.0	demand	even have grow over	year	0	0
1.0	his	have	class Yopougon neighbourhood	O	O
1.0	cat	be	eat in soup with degree spice	0	0
1.0	most people	even still think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	animal	will	will seasoned	0	0
1.0	Simone Gbale	be	36	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	cook	be with	complex	0	0
1.0	cat	be	eat in soup with degree spice to client 's taste accompany	0	0
1.0	cat	be eat in	soup	0	0
1.0	cat	be eat with	degree spice to client 's taste accompany by attieke	0	0
1.0	most people	still think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	people	even think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	he	gradually attract	high-class clientele	0	0
1.0	he 10-year-old youngest daughter	tend	fire	DURATION	0
1.0	his	have	side	O	O
1.0	dish	have enter	literature	0	0
1.0	work	have	cook	O	O
1.0	he	steal	cat himself	0	0
1.0	taboo	cook albeit	the meat	0	0
1.0	he	steal	local cat himself	0	0
1.0	client	to	taste accompany by attieke	0	0
1.0	he	build	reputation	0	0
1.0	man	have	powers	O	O
1.0	his	have	courtyard	O	O
1.0	fan	be in	he informed opinion	0	0
1.0	cat	be	eat in soup with degree spice to client 's taste accompany by attieke	0	0
1.0	dish	be book	brushing	0	0
1.0	people	even still think of	cat	0	0
1.0	most people	even think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	people	think of	cat	0	0
1.0	most people	think of	cat	0	0
1.0	people	still think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	crisis	have	time	O	O
1.0	friend	have	story	O	O
1.0	people	even think of	cat as domestic animal	0	0
1.0	client	have	taste	O	O
0.6924625296193697	the meat	cook	the meat	0	0
1.0	cat	be	eat	0	0
1.0	his	have	cleaver	O	O
1.0	pride	have	touch	O	O
1.0	people	still think of	cat as animal	0	0
1.0	earth	have	courtyard	O	O
1.0	Leon Sery	be	36	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	Leon Sery	be among	those	PERSON	0
1.0	state	have	capital	O	O
1.0	demand	have grow over	year	0	0
1.0	he	attract	high-class clientele	0	0
1.0	he 10-year-old daughter	tend	fire	DURATION	0
