1.0	it	be	transparent	0	0
1.0	he	suffer from	chest infection	0	0
1.0	mongolian model	be in	March next year	0	DATE
1.0	Razak	be in	police remand	PERSON	0
1.0	his	have	lawyers	O	O
1.0	court	say at_time	Friday	0	DATE
1.0	Abdul Razak	have	lover	PERSON	0
1.0	he	be grant	bail	0	0
1.0	High Court Judge K.N. Segara	have	lawyer	O	O
1.0	Mongolia	have	government	O	LOCATION
1.0	Razak	be in	now police remand	PERSON	DATE
1.0	analyst	have	home	O	O
1.0	he	be grant bail at_time	month	0	DATE
1.0	they	be oppose to	Abdul Razak	0	PERSON
1.0	they	be	oppose	0	0
1.0	whose	have	body	O	O
1.0	Her	have	remains	O	O
1.0	he lawyer	need	medical treatment	0	0
1.0	he lawyer	need	treatment	0	0
1.0	it	be transparent from	interference	0	0
1.0	woman	have	family	O	O
1.0	two police officer	both from	special Action Force	NUMBER	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Abdul Razak Baginda	abet	two policeman	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	His	have	lawyers	O	O
1.0	he	be grant bail on	274,348 dollar	0	MONEY
1.0	crimes	have	accused	O	O
1.0	Abdul Razak	have	lover	O	PERSON
1.0	model	have	slaying	O	O
1.0	his	have	bail conditions	O	O
1.0	Mongolia 's government	urge	Malaysia	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	he	be grant bail on	1.0 million ringgit deposit	0	MONEY
1.0	it	be transparent from	political interference	0	0
1.0	Mongolia	have	government	LOCATION	0
1.0	he	be grant bail at_time	last month	0	DATE
1.0	Abdul Razak Baginda	be	accuse	PERSON	0
