1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over month by opposition leader	PERSON	0
1.0	airport parking structure	have	ETA	ORGANIZATION	O
1.0	Spain	have	attorney general	O	LOCATION
1.0	its	have	sympathizers	O	O
0.9287495610055029	this	possibility of	tragedy	0	0
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over last few month by conservative opposition leader	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	Their	have	destiny	O	O
1.0	Candido Conde-Pumpio	say accord to	paper	PERSON	0
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over few month	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	conservative opposition leaders of taking a softer stance toward the armed separatist Basque group and its sympathizers in order to facilitate the peace process initiated by Prime Minister Jose Luis Rodriguez Zapatero	have see at	Madrid airport	0	LOCATION
1.0	tragedy	have	possibility	O	O
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over last few month by opposition leader	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	El Mundo	report at_time	Tuesday	ORGANIZATION	DATE
1.0	Spain	have	attorney general	LOCATION	0
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over few month by conservative opposition leader	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over last month by conservative opposition leader	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over few month by opposition leader	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over month	PERSON	0
1.0	bombing	be	serious	0	0
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over month by conservative opposition leader	PERSON	0
1.0	a serious act to which the state must respond in an energetic and decisive manner	have	authors	O	O
1.0	Spaniards	have	good-faith hopes	O	O
1.0	persons	have	death	O	O
1.0	its	have	burial	O	O
1.0	its author	will	will detain	0	0
1.0	campaign	have	course	O	O
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over last month	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over last month by opposition leader	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	Conde-Pumpio	have	have accuse over last few month	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	conservative opposition leaders of taking a softer stance toward the armed separatist Basque group and its sympathizers in order to facilitate the peace process initiated by Prime Minister Jose Luis Rodriguez Zapatero	have see with	bomb	0	0
