1.0	we	make	announcement	0	0
1.0	AirAsia	be	launch as budget carrier with two aircraft	ORGANIZATION	NUMBER
1.0	AirAsia	be	launch as budget carrier with just two aircraft	ORGANIZATION	NUMBER
1.0	AirAsia	one of	Asia 's most successful low-cost carrier	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	Malaysia 's budget carrier AirAsia	have	fleet	O	O
1.0	200	have	fleet size	O	NUMBER
1.0	fuel use	have	terms	O	O
1.0	jet	have	type	O	O
1.0	line	be with	ambitious route expansion plan	0	0
0.9715202504449502	AirAsia	one	Asia 's most successful low-cost carrier	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	budget carrier	be in	December 2001	0	DATE
1.0	we	make announcement by	end of January	0	DATE
1.0	AirAsia	be launch with	two aircraft	ORGANIZATION	NUMBER
1.0	carriers	have	one	NUMBER	O
1.0	we	make announcement by	end	0	DATE
1.0	AirAsia	be	launch as budget carrier in December 2001 with two aircraft	ORGANIZATION	NUMBER
1.0	report	have value deal base on	list price	0	0
1.0	Asia	of	most successful low-cost carrier	LOCATION	0
1.0	AirAsia	be	launch	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	AirAsia	have	fleet of 50 aircraft	LOCATION	NUMBER
0.9715202504449502	AirAsia	one	Asia 's successful low-cost carrier	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	Malaysia 's budget carrier AirAsia	say at_time	Friday	LOCATION	DATE
1.0	Asia	have	carriers	O	LOCATION
1.0	AirAsia	have	fleet	LOCATION	0
1.0	type	have	up made	O	O
1.0	aircraft	have	fleet	O	O
1.0	AirAsia	be launch with	just two aircraft	ORGANIZATION	NUMBER
1.0	AirAsia	be budget carrier of	Malaysia	ORGANIZATION	LOCATION
1.0	domestic route	be in	country	0	0
1.0	AirAsia	be launch as	budget carrier	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	Malaysia	have	AirAsia	LOCATION	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Airbus A320 ets	have	fleet	O	O
1.0	A320s	have	delivery	O	O
1.0	its	have	fleet	O	O
1.0	carrier Malaysia Airlines	have	route rationalisation	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	January	have	end	DATE	DATE
1.0	routes	have	bulk	O	O
0.9715202504449502	AirAsia	one of	Asia 's successful low-cost carrier	LOCATION	LOCATION
0.9715202504449502	AirAsia	one of	Asia 's most successful low-cost carrier	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	AirAsia	be	launch as budget carrier in December 2001 with just two aircraft	ORGANIZATION	NUMBER
1.0	aircraft	have	said	O	O
1.0	Malaysia	have	budget carrier AirAsia	ORGANIZATION	LOCATION
1.0	AirAsia	be launch as	budget carrier in December 2001	ORGANIZATION	DATE
