1.0	victim	have blame flash flood on	environmental degradation	0	0
1.0	Terengganu	have	states	O	LOCATION
1.0	situation	be in	Johor	0	LOCATION
1.0	we	be prepare for	worst situation	0	0
1.0	The latest victims	be	sweep	0	0
1.0	Che Moin Umar	chief of	crisis	PERSON	0
1.0	country	across	entire north	0	0
1.0	we	be prepare actually for	worst situation	0	0
1.0	victim	have blame	flash flood	0	0
1.0	people	have	number	O	O
1.0	Pahang	have	states	O	LOCATION
1.0	we	be prepare actually for	situation	0	0
1.0	country	have	north	O	O
1.0	flash flood	worst in	decade	0	0
1.0	devastation	be in	southern Johor state	0	LOCATION
1.0	downpours	have	warned	O	O
1.0	authority	forecast for	weekend	0	DATE
1.0	malaysian authority	forecast for	weekend	0	DATE
1.0	whose	have	bodies	O	O
1.0	crisis	have	chief	O	O
1.0	disaster management directorate	have	chief	O	O
1.0	situation	return to	normal	0	0
1.0	Friday	be in	northeastern state of Kelantan	DATE	LOCATION
1.0	victim	have blame	worst	0	0
1.0	victim	have blame flash flood on	degradation	0	0
1.0	The latest victims	be	when sweep away on Sunday	0	DATE
1.0	The latest victims	be	when sweep	0	0
1.0	Kelantan	have	states	O	LOCATION
1.0	The latest victims	be	sweep away on Sunday	0	DATE
1.0	victim	have blame	worst in decade	0	0
1.0	our	have	rescue boats	O	O
1.0	The latest victims	be	sweep away	0	0
1.0	The latest victims	be	when sweep away	0	0
1.0	situation	be in	south	0	0
1.0	we	be prepare for	situation	0	0
1.0	devastation	have	photographs	O	O
1.0	evacuees	have	number	O	O
1.0	Our	have	department	O	O
