1.0	ACF	be distribute	ration for World Food Programme	ORGANIZATION	ORGANIZATION
1.0	vehicles	have	five	NUMBER	O
1.0	ACF	be distribute	ration	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	December	have	night	TIME	DATE
1.0	several	be beat to	mock execution	0	0
1.0	Action Contre la Faim -LRB- Action Against Hunger -RRB-	have	employees	O	O
1.0	its	have	vehicles	O	O
1.0	several	be	in which beat	0	0
1.0	buildings	have	one	NUMBER	O
1.0	several	be	in which beat to mock execution	0	0
1.0	group	make to	Le Monde newspaper	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Sudan	have	Darfur region	O	LOCATION
1.0	attack	have	said	O	O
1.0	Aid workers who left the restive Darfur region of Sudan last month	have	several	O	O
1.0	Oxfam	have	workers	O	O
1.0	several	be	beat	0	0
0.7052703221580702	ACF	ration for	World Food Programme	ORGANIZATION	ORGANIZATION
