1.0	Macclesfield	boast	form	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	management style	have	asked	O	O
1.0	it	be	obviously different	0	0
1.0	Chelsea	have	standards	O	PERSON
1.0	premiership title	remain	Mourinho 's top priority	0	PERSON
1.0	famous trophy	be in	world	0	0
1.0	they	manager	Paul Ince	0	PERSON
1.0	their	have	players	O	O
1.0	top 2,000	rarely earn	they player	NUMBER	DURATION
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one of richest organisation in world football	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	form	have	run	O	O
1.0	his	have	management style	O	O
1.0	league	have	pressures	O	O
1.0	this	have add to	the Football League	0	0
1.0	day	have	rewards	O	DURATION
1.0	Paul Ince	have	result	O	PERSON
1.0	times	have	couple	O	O
1.0	Roman Abramovich	of	multi-billion pound fortune	PERSON	0
1.0	buzz	come as	result of Paul Ince	0	PERSON
1.0	Month award	have	Manager	O	O
1.0	organisations	have	one	NUMBER	O
1.0	it	be harder in	competition renown	0	0
1.0	staff	have	member	O	O
1.0	Macclesfield	certainly boast	better form	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	Saturday	have	FA Cup	DATE	MISC
1.0	Macclesfield	certainly boast	form	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	Mourinho	take charge in	2004	PERSON	DATE
1.0	unbeaten streak	have	courtesy	O	O
1.0	Saturday	have	FA Cup	MISC	DATE
1.0	Cup	be	intense	MISC	0
1.0	players	have	host	O	O
1.0	Macclesfield on a map	have	romance	O	O
1.0	it	imagine	starker contrast	0	0
1.0	it	be harder in	competition	0	0
1.0	pound fortune	have	back	O	O
1.0	third premiership title	remain	Mourinho 's priority	ORDINAL	PERSON
1.0	Chelsea	have grow on	back of Roman Abramovich 's pound fortune	PERSON	PERSON
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one of organisation	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	pundits	have	manager	O	O
1.0	it	be harder in	competition renown for its romance	0	0
1.0	buzz	come as	result	0	0
0.7149120287791494	competition	renown for	its romance	0	0
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one richest organisation in world football	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	richest organisation	be in	world football	0	0
1.0	it	obviously be different from	league	0	0
1.0	Macclesfield	of	staff	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	Macclesfield	have	staff	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Chelsea	have grow on	back	PERSON	0
1.0	Roman Abramovich	have	pound fortune	O	PERSON
1.0	minnows	have	one	NUMBER	O
1.0	premiership title	remain	Mourinho 's priority	0	PERSON
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one organisation in world football	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	Mourinho	have	priority	O	PERSON
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one organisation	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	it	be different from	league	0	0
1.0	games	have	loads	O	O
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one of richest organisation	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	it	be	harder	0	0
1.0	it	be	different	0	0
1.0	tie	be with	host of key player miss	0	0
1.0	it	imagine	contrast	0	0
1.0	Macclesfield	boast	better form	ORGANIZATION	0
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one richest organisation	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	Football League	have	bottom	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Chelsea	have grow on	back of Roman Abramovich 's multi-billion pound fortune	PERSON	PERSON
1.0	Jose Mourinho	have	arrival	O	O
1.0	Mourinho	take	charge	PERSON	0
1.0	Macclesfield	of	day	ORGANIZATION	DURATION
1.0	Chelsea	have grow into	one of organisation in world football	PERSON	NUMBER
1.0	top 2,000	earn	they player	NUMBER	DURATION
1.0	his	have	time	O	O
0.49939527238482123	we	have get in	club	0	0
1.0	football	have	minnows	O	O
1.0	bottom	have	lifted	O	O
1.0	Mourinho	have	top priority	PERSON	0
1.0	english football	of	genuine minnow	0	0
1.0	Macclesfield	have	day	DURATION	ORGANIZATION
1.0	third premiership title	remain	Mourinho 's top priority	ORDINAL	PERSON
