0.9283165518541037	Israel	be conduct by	Geocartographica Institute	LOCATION	ORGANIZATION
1.0	percent	believe regard	head	PERCENT	0
1.0	Israel	of	armed force	LOCATION	0
1.0	53 percent	believe regard	head	PERCENT	0
1.0	forces	have	head	O	O
1.0	programme	have	part	O	O
1.0	its	have	methodology	O	O
1.0	53 percent	believe regard	head of Israel 's armed force	PERCENT	LOCATION
1.0	war	have	resign	O	O
1.0	last year	in	month-long midsummer war	DATE	0
0.9283165518541037	Israel	be	conduct	LOCATION	0
1.0	Israel	have	forces	O	LOCATION
1.0	methodology	have	Details	O	O
1.0	percent	believe regard	General Dan Haloutz	PERCENT	PERSON
1.0	percent	believe regard	head of Israel 's armed force	PERCENT	LOCATION
1.0	percent	believe regard	head of Israel 's force	PERCENT	LOCATION
1.0	respondents	have	percent	PERCENT	O
1.0	their	have	country	O	O
1.0	year	have	midsummer war	O	DATE
1.0	53 percent	believe regard	General Dan Haloutz	PERCENT	PERSON
1.0	Dan Haloutz	head of	Israel 's armed force	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	new clash	be with	Hezbollah	0	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Hezbollah	be in	Lebanon	ORGANIZATION	LOCATION
1.0	53 percent	believe regard	head of Israel 's force	PERCENT	LOCATION
1.0	Israelis	have	percent	PERCENT	MISC
