1.0	the weapons	have	surrender	O	O
1.0	people	surrender	weapon	0	0
1.0	Gedi	be on	Monday	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Mogadishu	have	support	O	LOCATION
1.0	Mahamoud Hassan Ali	be	Mogadishu	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	line	be with	leader	0	0
1.0	government	have	support	0	0
1.0	line	be with	declaration of transitional federal government in consultation	0	0
1.0	government	have	declaration	O	O
1.0	government forces	have	wake	O	O
1.0	they	live with	weapon	0	0
1.0	mistrust	have	lot	O	O
1.0	Somalia	have	government	O	LOCATION
1.0	nobody	hand of	of arm to state	0	0
1.0	their	have	weapons	O	O
1.0	transitional federal government	be in	consultation	0	0
1.0	Gedi	order resident within	three day	PERSON	DURATION
1.0	Gedi	order resident to	hand in they weapon	PERSON	0
1.0	Gedi	order	resident	PERSON	0
1.0	nobody	hand of	of arm	0	0
1.0	Gedi	order resident to	hand	PERSON	0
1.0	Somalia	by	government disarm in capital Mogadishu	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	Gedi	order resident in	capital Mogadishu	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	Mahamoud Hassan Ali	be mayor of	Mogadishu	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	hand	be in	they weapon	0	0
1.0	government	have	support of Mogadishu	0	LOCATION
1.0	the capital Mogadishu	have	rehabilitation programme	O	LOCATION
1.0	we	use	force	0	0
1.0	Ali	say	refer	PERSON	0
1.0	the capital Mogadishu	have	control	O	LOCATION
1.0	force	have	use	O	O
