1.0	their	have	cheques	O	O
1.0	ethnic	have	allegations	O	O
1.0	Biafra	have	Republic	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	them	have	Some	O	O
0.902193790416284	Igbos	lead by	then Colonel Emeka Odumegwu-Ojukwu nigerian army	0	PERSON
1.0	Some of them who served the defunct Republic of Biafra	have	role	O	O
1.0	marginalisation	have	allegations	O	O
1.0	police	say at_time	Wednesday	0	DATE
1.0	neglect	have	allegations	O	O
0.902193790416284	Igbos	lead by	Colonel Emeka Odumegwu-Ojukwu nigerian army	0	PERSON
0.902193790416284	Igbos	lead by	Colonel Emeka Odumegwu-Ojukwu	0	PERSON
1.0	disease	have	mostly	O	O
0.902193790416284	Igbos	lead by	Colonel Emeka Odumegwu-Ojukwu army	0	PERSON
1.0	hunger	have	mostly	O	O
1.0	army	have	Colonel Emeka Odumegwu-Ojukwu	PERSON	O
0.902193790416284	Igbos	lead by	then Colonel Emeka Odumegwu-Ojukwu	0	PERSON
1.0	Igbos	launch	rebellion	0	0
1.0	police officers	have	total	O	O
0.902193790416284	Igbos	lead by	then Colonel Emeka Odumegwu-Ojukwu army	0	PERSON
