1.0	increase	exceed	expectation of economist	0	0
1.0	sale	rise	0.1 percent month-on-month	0	PERCENT
1.0	The EU 's Eurostat data agency	have	figures	O	O
1.0	0.4 percent	be in	November over October	PERCENT	DATE
1.0	economists	have	expectations	O	O
1.0	Slovenia	become	member of eurozone	LOCATION	0
1.0	percent	have	increase	O	PERCENT
1.0	Slovenia	become	13th member of eurozone	LOCATION	ORDINAL
1.0	Slovenia	member of	eurozone	LOCATION	0
1.0	eurozone	have	member	O	O
1.0	retail sale	be in	12 country use last year	0	DATE
1.0	Slovenia	become on	Monday	LOCATION	DATE
1.0	year-on	have	increase	O	O
1.0	Slovenia	13th member of	eurozone	LOCATION	0
1.0	increase	exceed	expectation of economist poll	0	0
1.0	EU	have	Eurostat datum agency	ORGANIZATION	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Slovenia	become	13th member	LOCATION	ORDINAL
1.0	EU	have	Eurostat data agency	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	Slovenia	become	member	LOCATION	0
1.0	increase	exceed	expectation	0	0
1.0	percent	have	year rise	O	PERCENT
