1.0	Somalia	also have	one mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	Osman Dufle	vice-president of	National Committee for Health Emergency Services	PERSON	ORGANIZATION
1.0	diseases	have	kinds	O	O
1.0	population	have	quarter	DURATION	O
1.0	health personnel	have	retirement age	O	O
0.7440882391399603	capacity fertile soil	deliver	health care	0	0
1.0	displaced person	be in	Mogadishu	DURATION	LOCATION
1.0	malaria	be	endemic	0	0
1.0	ill-health	have	kinds	O	O
1.0	government	have prepare	emergency health programme	0	0
1.0	percent	have	access	PERCENT	0
1.0	Somalia	suffer from	shortage	LOCATION	0
1.0	government	launch appeal to	humanitarian agency	0	0
1.0	people	have	numbers	O	O
1.0	malaria	be	where endemic	0	0
1.0	population	have	percent	PERCENT	O
1.0	artillery duels	have	weeks	DURATION	O
1.0	country	disintegrate with	ouster	0	0
1.0	Osman Dufle	minister in	Somalia 's transitional government	PERSON	LOCATION
1.0	its weak government	say on	Tuesday	0	DATE
1.0	Somalia	suffer from	shortage of medical personnel	LOCATION	0
1.0	Somalia	have	care system	O	O
0.7440882391399603	soil	extremely limited capacity of	health ministry	0	0
1.0	country	have	health infrastructure	O	O
1.0	Somalia	have	one highest maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	cholera	be rife with	300,000 victim	0	NUMBER
1.0	fighting	have	years	DURATION	O
1.0	government	urgently need	aid	0	0
1.0	Somalia	suffer from	shortage of personnel	LOCATION	0
1.0	malaria	endemic	diarrhea	0	0
1.0	cholera	be rife with	300,000 victim of civil war	0	NUMBER
1.0	cholera	be rife with	estimate 300,000 victim of war begin in 1991	0	NUMBER
1.0	government	need	international aid	0	0
1.0	its weak central government	say on	Tuesday	0	DATE
1.0	Somalia	have	one of mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	cholera	be rife with	estimate 300,000 victim of war begin	0	NUMBER
1.0	cholera	be rife with	300,000 victim of war	0	NUMBER
0.7440882391399603	capacity soil	deliver	health care	0	0
1.0	high infant	be with	downward trend see in past decade	0	DATE
1.0	country	be divide among	warlord	0	0
1.0	many	nurse of	doctor	0	0
1.0	government	urgently need	international aid	0	0
1.0	protracted civil strife	be in	country	0	0
1.0	Somalia	have	one of maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	finding	reveal	240 doctor	0	NUMBER
1.0	Islamists	be with	neighbouring Ethiopia 's military help	MISC	LOCATION
1.0	health personnel	have	terms	O	O
0.7440882391399603	soil	limited capacity of	health ministry	0	0
1.0	year	develop	tuberculosis	SET	0
1.0	Somalia	also have	one of highest maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
0.7440882391399603	fertile soil	capacity of	health ministry	0	0
1.0	Internally displaced persons in Mogadishu	have	homes	O	O
1.0	cholera	be rife with	estimate 300,000 victim	0	NUMBER
1.0	poorest	have	one	NUMBER	O
1.0	country	disintegrate with	ouster of dictator Mohamed Siad Barre	0	PERSON
1.0	cholera	be rife with	300,000 victim of war begin	0	NUMBER
1.0	government	launch	appeal	0	0
1.0	Africa nation	have	Horn	LOCATION	O
1.0	Somalia	also have	one of maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	its government	say on	Tuesday	0	DATE
1.0	country	be	divide	0	0
1.0	city	have	population	O	O
1.0	Somalia	also have	one maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	Somalia	also have	one highest mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
0.7440882391399603	limited capacity fertile soil	deliver	health care	0	0
1.0	doctors	have	nurses	O	O
1.0	its central government	say on	Tuesday	0	DATE
1.0	Somalia	suffer from	dangerous shortage of personnel	LOCATION	0
1.0	dictator Mohamed Siad Barre	have	ouster	O	PERSON
1.0	war	have	victims	O	O
1.0	Ethiopia	have	help	O	LOCATION
1.0	cholera	be rife with	300,000 victim of civil war begin	0	NUMBER
1.0	malaria	endemic	cholera	0	0
1.0	cholera	be rife with	estimate 300,000 victim of civil war	0	NUMBER
1.0	less percent	have	access to drinking water	PERCENT	0
1.0	present	have	demands	O	DATE
1.0	Osman Dufle	tell	AFP	PERSON	ORGANIZATION
1.0	capacity	make	soil	0	0
1.0	cases	have	percent	PERCENT	O
1.0	cholera	be rife with	estimate 300,000 victim of civil war begin	0	NUMBER
1.0	mortality rates	have	one	NUMBER	O
1.0	which	have	forced	O	O
1.0	National Committee	have	Vice-President	O	ORGANIZATION
1.0	kinds	have	spread	O	O
1.0	health services	have	demands	O	O
1.0	Somalia	have	government	O	LOCATION
1.0	10 million	have	nation	O	NUMBER
0.7440882391399603	fertile soil	limited capacity of	health ministry	0	0
1.0	country	have	health infrastructure	0	0
1.0	cholera	be rife with	estimate 300,000 victim of war	0	NUMBER
1.0	cholera	be	rife	0	0
1.0	Somalia	have	one mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	woes	have	end	O	O
1.0	cholera	rife	tuberculosis	0	0
0.7440882391399603	soil	capacity of	health ministry	0	0
1.0	junior health minister	be in	Somalia 's transitional government	0	LOCATION
1.0	year	develop tuberculosis in	Somalia	SET	LOCATION
1.0	cholera	be rife with	300,000 victim of civil war begin in 1991	0	NUMBER
1.0	personnel	have	shortage	O	O
1.0	AIDS	have	spread	O	MISC
1.0	less percent	have	access	PERCENT	0
1.0	Somalia	also have	one of mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	limited capacity	make	soil	0	0
1.0	percent	have	access to drinking water	PERCENT	0
1.0	government report	be in	November	0	DATE
1.0	Somalia	in	transitional government	LOCATION	0
1.0	health ministry	have	capacity	O	O
1.0	Somalia	have	one of highest maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	Somalia	have	one highest mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	cholera	be rife with	300,000 victim of war begin in 1991	0	NUMBER
1.0	country	disintegrate into	lawlessness	0	0
1.0	government	need	aid	0	0
1.0	capacity	make	fertile soil	0	0
1.0	cholera	rife	malaria	0	0
1.0	territories	have	control	O	O
0.7440882391399603	fertile soil	extremely limited capacity of	health ministry	0	0
1.0	east african country	one of	poorest in world	0	0
1.0	deprivation	have	result	O	O
1.0	limited capacity	make	fertile soil	0	0
1.0	poverty	have	result	O	O
1.0	Ethiopia	with	military help	LOCATION	0
1.0	cholera	be rife with	estimate 300,000 victim of civil war begin in 1991	0	NUMBER
1.0	Somalia	also have	one of highest mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	displaced people	be in	Somalia	0	LOCATION
1.0	Tuesday	have	government	O	O
1.0	Somalia	also have	one highest maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	conditions	have	numbers	O	O
1.0	government	launch appeal to	agency	0	0
1.0	health hazard	have	dimension	O	O
1.0	Somalia	suffer from	dangerous shortage	LOCATION	0
0.7440882391399603	limited capacity soil	deliver	health care	0	0
1.0	the Islamists	have	fall	DATE	MISC
1.0	year	be	estimate	SET	0
1.0	Somalia	have	one maternal mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
1.0	malaria	endemic	tuberculosis	0	0
1.0	Somalia	suffer from	dangerous shortage of medical personnel	LOCATION	0
1.0	Somalia	have	one of highest mortality rate	LOCATION	NUMBER
