1.0	Nuri al-Maliki	be on	Saturday	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Hosni Mubarak	be from	egyptian	PERSON	0
1.0	decision	be	implement	0	0
1.0	sedition interference	be in	internal affair of Iraq feeling of family of victim	0	LOCATION
1.0	people	have	enemies	O	O
1.0	Two former Saddam henchmen -- Barzan Ibrahim al-Tikriti and Awad Ahmed al-Bandar --	be find	guilty	DATE	0
1.0	Maliki in his first reaction to the ousted president 's hanging in Baghdad on December 30	speak at	ceremony on 86th anniversary of army	PERSON	DATE
1.0	victims	have	families	O	O
1.0	Maliki in his first reaction to the ousted president 's hanging in Baghdad on December 30	speak at	ceremony on anniversary	PERSON	DATE
1.0	people	have	wish	O	O
1.0	Saddam	have	hanging	O	PERSON
1.0	Iraqi Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki on Saturday	have	reaction	O	O
1.0	iraqi Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki	review	relation	PERSON	0
1.0	the 1980	in dujail be	Dujail	DATE	LOCATION
1.0	iraqi Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki	threaten	say	PERSON	0
1.0	Maliki	be in	he first reaction to oust president 's hanging	PERSON	ORDINAL
1.0	Saddam Hussein	have	execution	O	PERSON
1.0	army	have	anniversary	DATE	O
1.0	leaders	have	number	O	O
1.0	Two former Saddam henchmen -- Barzan Ibrahim al-Tikriti and Awad Ahmed al-Bandar --	be	find	DATE	0
1.0	Baghdad	be on	December 30	LOCATION	DATE
1.0	Maliki in his first reaction to the ousted president 's hanging in Baghdad on December 30	speak at	ceremony on anniversary of iraqi army	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Saddam	have	hanging	PERSON	0
1.0	dictator	have	execution	O	O
1.0	Maliki in his first reaction to the ousted president 's hanging in Baghdad on December 30	speak at	ceremony on 86th anniversary of iraqi army	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Two former Saddam henchmen -- Barzan Ibrahim al-Tikriti and Awad Ahmed al-Bandar --	be find along	guilty	DATE	0
1.0	Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki	threaten	say	PERSON	0
1.0	the country	have	institutions	O	O
1.0	hanging	be	internal	0	0
1.0	Dujail	north of	Baghdad on December 30	LOCATION	LOCATION
1.0	Maliki in his first reaction to the ousted president 's hanging in Baghdad on December 30	speak at	ceremony on 86th anniversary	PERSON	DATE
1.0	families	have	Iraq abuses feelings	O	O
1.0	Maliki in his first reaction to the ousted president 's hanging in Baghdad on December 30	speak at	ceremony	PERSON	0
1.0	regime	have	officials	O	O
1.0	innocents	have	blood	O	O
1.0	Dujail	be in	the 1980	LOCATION	DATE
1.0	Two former Saddam henchmen -- Barzan Ibrahim al-Tikriti and Awad Ahmed al-Bandar --	be	find along with Saddam	DATE	PERSON
1.0	The Iraqi government	have	relations	O	O
1.0	oust president	to	hanging in Baghdad on December 30	0	DATE
1.0	Maliki in his first reaction to the ousted president 's hanging in Baghdad on December 30	speak at	ceremony on anniversary of army	PERSON	DATE
1.0	Iraq abuses feelings	have	affairs	O	O
1.0	Prime Minister Nuri al-Maliki	review	relation	PERSON	0
1.0	Baghdad on December 30	have	north	O	LOCATION
1.0	Two former Saddam henchmen -- Barzan Ibrahim al-Tikriti and Awad Ahmed al-Bandar --	be	find along	DATE	0
1.0	Nuri al-Maliki	be	iraqi	PERSON	0
1.0	whose	have	hands	O	O
1.0	president	have	hanging	O	O
1.0	despot	have	execution	O	O
1.0	a guard	have	moments	O	O
